Perfect.
>> It looks like it's only Kim and
Harrison, though, so you guys can just
fire away.
>> All right, cool. Hey, Nick. Good to see
you again.
>> Good to see you guys. Good to see you.
>> Good to see you. So, first of all, like
what what do you anticipate your role
being this year? And like what have they
talked to you about with what they see?
>> Uh yeah, I mean, obviously, uh I'm
coming in here to compete. Um we got a
lot of stuff to figure out. Obviously,
over the next few days, they'll be
adding some more pieces. So, uh, I know
that I can play, you know, center, right
guard, left guard, uh, whatever it is, I
want to compete for a spot. I I really,
if that, you know, depending on what
they do, if that center job is something
I can compete for, that's that's
something that I want to do. Um, really,
really enjoy one, just getting the
chance to compete for a spot. Um, and,
you know, center's a position I played a
long time. um haven't had a ton of
opportunities uh to play since I got to
the NFL. So, if if that opportunity is
there, would love it. Um if not, just
excited to be back. I mean, it's a a
really good building. Um really excited
for for Stape um and Shane who are, you
know, guys that were, you know, Stape's
been awesome the last two years and
Shane I've known since I was [snorts] 20
years old at Illinois. So, uh really
excited for both of them. State
definitely deserve this opportunity and
and Shane as well. So excited for them.
I'm excited to have, you know, WY back
as well already um in the offensive line
room and hopefully uh add a few add a
few more new pieces, maybe keep some
guys not sure about all that. But um I
like the room we have so far and
hopefully add a few more pieces over the
next couple days.
>> And what if if you go to center like
what do you like about that? What suits
you at that position? Uh I think the
like my my biggest the biggest element
of it for me is the leadership role that
centers are almost required to have you
know before Jay gets the play call gets
in the huddle um you know it's it's my
huddle if I'm at center and uh just
getting the boys ready getting the boys
right for when uh Jay is in the huddle
uh communicating at the line of
scrimmage um it's really the one spot
you know it's like if you're at guard
You obviously have your tackle, your
center, you talk with the other guard.
You're kind of too far away from the
other tackle to communicate much. At
center, you really get to communicate to
all five. Um, occasionally the tight
ends, quarterback, you really get to I
get to use those
the skills and, you know, the things
I've learned uh in the mental side of uh
football um probably the most at center.
So, I really enjoy that. Um, and then
just that's that's the position I I've
always played. Uh, I was a center my
entire childhood, all of high school,
and then, you know, at Illinois, my last
seven years in the league, I've always
kind of been in that whether I was
starting or not, it was always kind of
the backup center. Um, so I love that
role. Um, I'm comfortable in it. Um, and
you know, if that's a if that's open,
that's an opportunity. Would love to
compete for that.
>> Hey, Nick, congrats, man. Welcome back.
Um,
>> I asked Andrew this question. I'm going
ask you the same question. You guys have
been together uh all but but one year
really since you joined forces in Kansas
City. How impactful is it for you to
have him back along with you this
season?
>> Uh it's awesome. Um I mean Big Wise is
uh
yeah he you know he's he's he's like
family um to myself and really my entire
family um and his as well. They're I
think they're going to be coming out to
my parents house probably in a few
weeks. Uh Wy and I did a few uh
split a few bourbon barrels together. Um
so he's going to come over, pick up his
cases, and you know, we'll spend a day
together. And just a good human being.
Uh dude, I've been fortunate enough to
be around uh for now, you know, seven
years of my my eight eight years in the
NFL. Um good human being from a good
family. Got the same Midwest values. So,
uh, that that was, uh, seeing him sign
and then being able to sign and stay.
That's pretty cool because, you know, I
was told, uh, a long time ago by an old
Illinois
player that played in the NFL and
basically said like it's it's hard to
make friends in the NFL. You know,
you're not going to be able to make a
lot of them. Um, so the fact that able
to, you know, make a have made quite a
few friends in the NFL, which fortunate
enough to be around long enough, but to
make a a really good friend like that
that I consider family, uh, pretty
special.
>> Yeah. And and obviously a lot of changes
are expected this season for you guys
from scheme to obviously the roster
tournament. Like you just kind of
reference every single offseason. Are
you a person that really kind of
embraces the changes and maybe even gets
excited for the new or or kind of how do
you balance your emotions with those
things on the horizon?
>> Uh yeah, I mean the obviously the locker
rooms every you know you get to those
last two weeks of the year and a
sentiment that was shared with me early
uh that I try to share now with with
some of the younger guys is like the
locker room will never be the same. So
enjoy the last few weeks because it
truly
it changes every year. You lose, you
know, close friends, good relationships,
and new guys come in and the dynamic
changes every year. Um, so always
excited to see, you know, guys that we
retained. Obviously, Tres is, you know,
huge part of this community. Uh, I've
seen Dise as well signed, which is
awesome. What a just incredible human
being. Um, and a few other guys as well.
So, keeping some guys around is awesome.
Excited to see the new guys. Um, and
then staffwise, I mean, I'm not sure if
we even talking about that, but
blow. I mean, that's uh an awesome hire.
That was one of those guys that I knew,
you know, DQ had texted the uh offensive
line and quarterbacks when that news was
going to break. and one of those that I
knew the the media would have a lot of
questions and um just because he's a
it's a young hireer obviously but I met
him uh obviously played against him five
times at Purdue at Illinois um I think
he got the better of us four of those
five which sucks but so I knew knew him
from there respected him from there and
then he was actually one of our
quarterbacks at the East West Shrine
game um through the draft process and
immediately was like man this guy he's
the reason that Purdue was able to have
some success while he while he was
there. Um had a big win over Ohio State
when he was there. He's just the right
the right guy that you want
in the building. Loves loves what he's
doing. Um has his priorities straight.
Um loves
loves football. Um and there's you could
say that about a lot of people in this
league, but just a guy that he's a guy
that truly loves what he's doing. um and
deserves this opportunity. So, really
excited for him. Um really excited to
help uh you know, in whatever way I can
help the off, you know, the offensive
line learn the new system. Um but I'm
really really excited for uh the the
future with him at uh OC.
>> And you've been on the one side of free
agency. We're trying to figure out your
future, what's next for you and your
family. Being on this side of free
agency where you have your contract, you
know where you're going to be playing in
2026. What do you what's what's your
focus this week? Do you pay attention
move by move or do you just kind of get
the updates in general or how much do
you pay attention to it or not at all?
>> Um, yeah, I I definitely pay attention
to it uh on a team basis and leaguewide.
Um, one for the guys we're bringing in.
Excited to see who we're bringing in and
two for the guys that uh that that we
can't bring back. Um, that's one of my
my favorite parts about the league is
when guys have to depart cuz we couldn't
keep them or another team was willing to
give them more. Um, it's always there's
always so much excitement for that guy.
Like it's this league's tough. It's hard
to stick around for one year, let alone,
you know, make it to that second
contract or third contract, whatever it
is. And it's always so it's always so
exciting to see those guys that are they
have put time in, put the work in, um,
and are able to go get themselves and
and their family taken care of for a
long time. So, love that part of it. And
then the, you know, the the football
nerd uh, side of me, the the contract, I
I I do love seeing seeing the markets
and seeing if I have any type of idea of
what guys are worth and um, what they're
going to sign for. So, always intrigued
um uh to see how those deals work out
cuz it's, you know, this is my job. It
is my profession, but there's still the
the football, you know, fan side of me
as well that that loves seeing uh that
that side of it, too.
>> Awesome. Thanks, Nick. Congrats again,
man.
>> Appreciate you. Thank you.
>> Anybody else?
>> All right. Thanks, Nick.
>> All righty. Thanks, guys.
Where's the thing? Okay, you're good.
>> Y
this light is so bright. All right,
you're I don't know what you need to do
now, but
>> I guess I'll just bring you back to the
lobby.
I guess
>> we can go this way.